[
    {
        "question": "How many time zones are there in the contiguous United States?",
        "answer": "Four"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the `fluff` in the Massachusetts fluffernutter sandwich?",
        "answer": "Marshmallow -- The fluffernutter is a simple sandwich, made with marshmallow fluff and peanut butter between two slices of bread."
    },
    {
        "question": "Word of mouth made which food cart sandwich famous?",
        "answer": "Philly cheesesteak -- The cheesesteak is quintessentially Philadelphia food."
    },
    {
        "question": "Nashville, Tennessee is widely considered the birthplace of which dish?",
        "answer": "Hot chicken -- While versions exist all over Nashville, hot chicken first showed up on the menu at Prince`s Hot Chicken Shack."
    },
    {
        "question": "The lobster roll is a summer staple in which part of the U.S.?",
        "answer": "New England -- It takes all the hard work out of eating lobster \u2014 freeing the meat from its shell and loading it on a bun."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where will you find an island with a name that translates to `Coffee Club.`",
        "answer": "Greenland -- Kaffeklubben Island is another landform named for the beloved caffeinated beverage."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what sea would you find the Admiralty Islands?",
        "answer": "Bismarck Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Cape will you find at the tip of Africa?",
        "answer": "Cape of Good Hope"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Asian capital was formerly known as Batavia?",
        "answer": "Jakarta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is made up of 3,000 islands, the largest being Honshu, Hokkaido, Kyushu and Shikoku?",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is Seattle`s sister city in Japan?",
        "answer": "Kobe"
    },
    {
        "question": "What tiny island makes the curling stones used in the Olympics?",
        "answer": "Ailsa Craig, Scotland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Hawaiian island is entirely privately owned?",
        "answer": "Ni`ihau (The island was purched by wealthy Scottish plantation owners from King Kamehameha V in 1864 for $10,000 in gold.)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sport is strangely associated with Christmas in Venezuela?",
        "answer": "Many Venezuelans traditionally roller-skate during Christmas."
    },
    {
        "question": "What territory`s flag features three armored legs?",
        "answer": "Isle of Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which port city was the first capital of Pakistan?",
        "answer": "Karachi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Father Damien ministered to lepers on which Hawaiian Island?",
        "answer": "Molokai"
    },
    {
        "question": "The river Liffey flows through the centre of which European city?",
        "answer": "Dublin, Ireland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the `click`-based Xhosa language spoken?",
        "answer": "South Africa -- Xhosa is one of at least 35 indigenous languages spoken there. It is a member of the Bantu family of languages."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the capital of Michigan before Lansing?",
        "answer": "Detroit -- Due to Detroit`s proximity to Canada, a perceived threat at the time, Lansing became the state`s capital in 1847."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is home to the colorful Rainbow Mountain?",
        "answer": "Peru -- AKA Vinicunca, it achieves its vibrant hues thanks to natural weathering, which has exposed mineral strips in the earth."
    },
    {
        "question": "What geothermal Icelandic site has the same name as a 1980 movie?",
        "answer": "Blue Lagoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which universities` mascots are the same as their state`s animal?",
        "answer": "Wisconsin, Oregon, Texas, UCLA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state has a diamond illustrated on its license plate?",
        "answer": "Arkansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country will you find a peninsula called `Land`s End`?",
        "answer": "England"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has the oldest continuously used national flag?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Managua is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Nicaragua"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Togo?",
        "answer": "Lome"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lome is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Togo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lome is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Togo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What three countries border the Togolese Republic?",
        "answer": "Ghana, Benin and Burkina Faso"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country has the calling code +20?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with Monaco?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that shares a land border with San Marino?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 3 letter code for O`Hare International Airport?",
        "answer": "ORD"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two colors are in the flag of Austria?",
        "answer": "Red and white"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sleeping Bear Dunes National Park is located along the shores of what lake?",
        "answer": "Lake Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official state animal of the US state of Oregon?",
        "answer": "The beaver"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is known as the `Breadbasket of America`?",
        "answer": "Kansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Bay State`?",
        "answer": "Massachusetts"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Santa Clara Valley is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Northern Tropic also called?",
        "answer": "Tropic of Cancer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the Northern and Southern tropics also known as?",
        "answer": "Tropic of Cancer and Tropic of Capricorn"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which hemisphere is the Tropic of Cancer located?",
        "answer": "Northern"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which hemisphere is the Tropic of Capricorn located?",
        "answer": "Southern"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the three colors on the German flag?",
        "answer": "Black, red, and gold"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which pass connects Afghanistan to Pakistan?",
        "answer": "The Khyber Pass"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s first underwater hotel?",
        "answer": "Maldives"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. state is famous for its bluebonnets?",
        "answer": "Texas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city was founded by Brigham Young in 1847?",
        "answer": "Salt Lake City"
    }
]